I've been missing in my sleep
He's eating steak, somewhere in the middle they both take a break
He'd trade his knife stick for a fishing pole
Chase her laughter like it's his patrol, oh Paige
Don't you know you're the catch of the day
And this cop's got one hell of a line to say
sweet song so anyway you know what that uh that jackass that keeps doing that to my show
an ugly person. That's all I got to say about that. So anyway. Oh well. Okay next, there you go.
If Karma's a bitch, I hope she will be to him.
He marries her.
Make him marry her.
Okay, pins. No, it's a good Alex. Honestly, it's a good song. So it's a good song
That's why I made it to the video. I was like, that's a chicken song. It needs to be in the video. So I
Want to make other videos this kind of expensive though. I mean, it's like
I think I paid quite a bit to make those two videos the two the two main videos
Anyway, I wasn't gonna continue past 1 a.m. because it was like
Yeah, you know, I don't think I don't think it's the same person
Yeah, so I don't know how long I was gonna be here like I was like, you know, I wanted to I said I'd say it
I say that I'd say it's like five people donated five dollars
It's a couple people said they would and nobody did and so I was about to wrap it up anyway
But then it was like oh Sam and it's not Tony. It's not I know it's not
But anyway
Yeah, I know for a fact it's not I know I know I mean it's like yeah, it did sound like him at first
But I now seem to trust me. It's fine. I
Know you might not believe me, but
No, it's not coming. No, it's not but now but I do want to play the ghost song because
He interrupted it like all the time. So I just want to play it without interruptions. So thank you
I
Alice is backstage. That's not you. That's not that's someone named someone different name
That's how you go straight or Alice. It's not you
I know no back but backstage there's somebody that's it says nypd runs new york. That's how you Alice
Using your same avatar
Hey, you got called out sorry by the they left it was it was calling you again
Almost I almost let him on actually I almost did but yeah, he took your avatar and it was the name Tommy Tame
So
Okay, I'm gonna play the rest of the song then
down just right
Press the song!
Who is the Alexander and White Beauty?
Is that you Alice? Okay.
You hear the last part said,
Okay girls, I believe you, maybe.
Okay, that's him.
I don't like when people try to imitate me and shit, so someone came up with my avatar?
Yeah, your exact avatar and it said NYPD runs NYC and then it was like the name Tami Tame or Tommy Tame or something?
That's crazy. That was on me.
It'll always be out of town in McQueen and WAPD. It'll never see
It was the last second. I was like, oh my god, you know, I like I like I stopped I almost accidentally put you on but
Yeah
It just happened, you know, I think it is honestly psyched. I'm not even fucking around. I think it's easy
Easy does not like me up here any way shape or form even in the chat
one CC's outside of McQueen, he's gonna, he plumbed you 10 minutes ago
because I started
those Tony's voice
it's either Tony or easy
I know when he says the end, I know when he says the end, I know his voice because he's like, he's come up several times and done it
so I know his voice exactly
I don't know, I heard Ghost and Tony go at it at the same time
so I was like, wow, it's not him, but whatever
I don't I don't know. It doesn't even matter. They sound alike. I think it's like
Maybe it's just like their accent or something is like similar. They have like a similar kind of
They were all together and they were like fighting each other. They were like talking, you know, right? So it can't be him
Yeah
You're right. It can't be like nobody has done good of a voice box like that you can like
Double your voice and fight each other like that's AI to the fullest. Yeah
Yes, too much
Sorry
Well, that's gonna start the next the next war probably is like some fake AI video that everyone's gonna believe and then it's gonna like
It's gonna be like fake at the last minute like but it's like it's gonna be too late at that point because the war's not
You started over it and it's gonna be like right
But it will be like so realistic of a of a AI
Like that will pass like through like the first yeah, it's scary bro. Yeah, it's scary
it you can't even tell what's real or not anymore that's how good it is
yeah
you know you can watch a video and think it's like a real person and say hi
like that's how good it's been I watched this thing like like a few years ago before like it was like
real big they had like you know some principal at a school they had him like uh you know so someone
sent some message to teachers and it was like oh the principal caught on tape and it was like the
They can clone you your voice and like the fame you
They can do that
And then you have to fight it like if that wasn't me like that's crazy
Yeah, and then I said, well, we have you on videotape doing it like right
It's like can you believe anything anymore? Like really it's like
Yeah, he'll you really have to like watch now. Like is that real or fake? That's the world we're living in
right
that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that's why I'm saying that
money and technology to get to
Not even that expensive though. It's like you can that people were talking to chat GPT about oh legal things and hacking and then
There's people you could hire and all I mean it's all kinds of million things, right?
And so it's like and are these like the most trustworthy people that are gonna give you the right information, you know
It's like a big shit. No
You know, no
Exactly
That pissed me off. You know, I was in the chat and then you were like you're backstage like I'm like that's not me
Bro, that's not me. Yeah
Well, I was attacking somebody I was attacking ghost to write saying he was Tony
So it's either him
Like somebody's like fuck you Alex and they try to come up as me to like fuck shit up
Yeah, that's just not random. You got to think of it that way if you're an FBI agent think about it like
Here's what he does he here you heard me say
Oh, you know or you heard you say in the chat you're gonna come up and so it's like oh it looks like you're gonna come up
But he didn't even be used your exact avatar like the exact when you have yeah, that's the interesting thing on earth
Bro, all you have to do is screenshot it right and then it goes into your picture album
And then you can make an account and then when you choose the picture you go into your
Scrolling thing and you put that avatar up. That is the easiest thing on the planet
That's like, you know, monkey cloning one-on-one, it can come up with your avatar, everybody's avatar.
That is so easy to do.
You just take a picture right now a screenshot of us right now. You can zoom in it and make my avatar your kid
It's easy cameras on psyche. I'm sorry to break it to you. Well, who knows I mean, I say I don't know
No, no, I know trust me dick. Okay, you don't want to listen ever though
You said flirty diving was burrow
Was burrow by the way burrow no no I got more intel on burrow burrow is raging demon
Oh my god, isn't that insane?
Great it doesn't that blow your mind
Burrow is
It's a mental ask me how ask me how tell me
The other day on some random panel he didn't know I was listening Regent Demon was up there
Doing his Regent Demon shit and all of a sudden
He turned into burdo
He went into burdo mode and he just became burdo and I'm listening to this. I'm like, oh my god. Oh
My god, he just turned. I'm like, yo Regent burdo's Regent Demon was burdo somebody
Birdo's not just some like random tranny that blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah
he brought her out
and I was like, holy s**t
people are crazy
yeah, they are
yeah, they are, man
that's like 99% fact
you know, there's always a 1% you gotta deal with
but uh
that's the one that's that's that's going out there to make a call the other people a lot you know different people like this person's this like he's fucking say
You know there's one this one. I'm confident on how can I be sick though? I mean next week really?
No, I'm kidding. I'm trying to like tell you an example
You know of how far I go off the edge sometimes and say shit like that
But that is just fact raging demon was like you're he was raging demon like you walk that baby
And then all of a sudden he just um somebody triggered him, and then he just started burning out like yo
what I mean believe me or not you know I don't have proof because I didn't I don't
have a video to just have to take my word on it's hard to have proof but I mean
the thing is I'm sure that there are people in the community that are multiple
people like I'm like a hundred percent sure right I just don't know I just don't
know if you're right about these what I don't know I just don't know you know man
and sometimes I'm off
Honestly, but when I'm right, you can admit that you can admit that you can admit that that's good. Yeah. No, I'm all for a lot of times
I've called summer
Multiple people and it's summer. I used to call summer little Shana and all these other bitches
Because they sound alike and you know, I like connect the dots and then I'm like, alright, it's not it's not this person
Like I was wrong
But sometimes I'm right and they hit it right on the money
Like 20 30% you know what I'm saying, but when I hit I hit and
The other night I heard him man. He turned into a bird. Oh, bro
I was like what the fuck no one no one could do that no one can be birdo and
It was the raging demon just and he turned into it and I was like holy shit
I even told beat about it like two nights ago
And she got pissed at me like she wouldn't believe me. She doesn't want to believe it. She was like, no
I'm like, yo, great. Your name is bird. Oh, I don't know man
She was dealing with him for like a lot like both of them for a long time
Oh wait, didn't you tell me that he'd like fall in love with flirty diamonds? So he's a trainee
He's like a gay guy. So he could be bird. Oh, you know that that's more
But uh, but burdo's American and like I don't think raising demons that's right
You don't know what burdo is honestly, right?
I've been told that he I've been told that he's it's a mean I'm obviously it's a he but I've been told he's
Whatever I don't want to push the issue man. I just heard that motherfucker turn into burdo
Okay, well, it's like maybe they sound alike
Somehow
Well interesting theory, but it's like um, but have you been Alice yet while? Yes. Yes interesting theory exactly
And that's where I want to leave it
Okay, I got a lot of theories about a lot of people and who they are with their soccer counts and multiple like personalities
Sometimes I'm right. Sometimes I'm wrong
But when I'm right, I'm right, baby
So I'm saying it's like a shocker like holy shit. You're right
a lot of times I'm wrong though. I'm going to go like 30%. I'm right. Cause I said some
crazy shit. This person's this person, this person's that person. And then I figured
out I'm like, all right. But sometimes I'm like, they, I hit it. And they're like, whoa,
yeah, it is that person. And kaboom, that outweighs the 80% when I'm wrong. You know what I mean?
like bro if you can figure out one asshole up here fucking going crazy with multiple
Accounts and different voices like that's worth gold. I
Don't care if you were wrong 30 times if you hit one that's gold
Well, I mean
gold like how like what what's it gonna do like if it really doesn't do anything
It's gold because it's exposed to the fullest. You just you know imagine
Regiment what's wrong?
Imagine all right. I'm tripping and I'm wrong, but imagine I'm right
That's not gold
Right imagine it's not really to say it's like an old thing imagine
No, it's not it doesn't seem like it's gold because it doesn't seem like it would be if any benefits like oh shut up
What are you trying to counter my mind now? So you're not gonna win dick
I always win shit head. Okay, imagine me telling you sick is actually fucking
Blogger right and uh, I'm wrong or maybe I'm right
If I'm right brother that one hit is worth gold
That's what I'm trying to say. That's all a little bit. It's gonna be a little bit dumb. Okay. This is one something else
And not saying you're dumb, but I'm just I think you mean he's a fucking trainee. Look at her. That's a man with a wig
Alex that's not a girl
You see her shoulders that bitch is a linebacker. You need a linebacker
Oh
Get up and show me your body. I'm sick of seeing your fat. I'll be face
Shut the fuck up. And if you're not you're a man. No, thank you, you pervert. I'm sorry. I'm sorry you mean
But yeah, let's leave it in Minecraft Alex. No, no, no, no, no, no, that's very inappropriate
I don't know why he does that like he just like goes arts going out first. He's like
Like how how many how many this is this is what this is what what does the Audi ever did to me?
He trusts, he believes, he believes with people crab that my hair is a fake.
I don't know, I don't get it, that's why I, I decide to step away from these people.
Sorry, you're a pervert, Mr. Alex.
You're a pervert.
Never I never doing and never doing the gathered things is in this YouTube
I just want to socialize with people new people like the society in Fira
Misdeme and everyone
I know she was just kidding she was just kidding she didn't mean that she was
Take your speech
I'm sorry, Mr. Psyche. I didn't mean it.
Well, maybe it's been a little bit of an emotional night.
I'm just going to wrap it up.
Thank you, Yumi. Thank you, Chat and everybody.
Thank you for being here.
Thank you. Bye-bye.
Thank you.